talentexchange.com 2012-11-05

# Data Privacy | TalentExchange

**Talent Exchange Website Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Statement is effective September 1st, 2011 and only applies to data gathered on the www.talentexchange.com web site or through the Taleo Radar application (collectively referred to herein as the "Talent Exchange"), and does not apply to any other information or web site. Please review this Privacy Statement periodically as we (Taleo Corporation) may update it from time to time and notify you by posting a revised statement on the Talent Exchange or otherwise. Each time you visit the Talent Exchange or provide us with information, you are, by doing so, accepting the terms and practices described in the Privacy Statement and Terms of Use at that time. 

The Talent Exchange is a portal for the online exchange of employment related information.  Any information you submit to the Talent Exchange will be published and available for access, download and further processing by other users of the Talent Exchange. We do not promise any confidentiality or privacy restrictions and **you should have** **no expectation of privacy with respect to data you share via the talent exchange**. Be careful about the information you publish. Generally, other users of the Talent Exchange should not have a need to request the following data from you and we recommend that you not upload such data to the Talent Exchange:

  * • social security number (or other government issue identification number); 
  * • drivers license number;
  * • credit card information;
  * • bank account information;
  * • medical history or medical records; and 
  * • credit history or credit information.

**Taleo does not conduct or require criminal background checks with respect to any Users of the Talent Exchange. As with any exchange of personal data, you should exercise caution and due care before sharing personal information like your address or physical location with another Talent Exchange User. As a result of using the Taleo Radar application, you may be disclosing your physical location publicly.** **.**  

**Access to Personal Information.   **In order to operate the Talent Exchange in an efficient and effective manner, we collect personal information, including contact information such as your first and last name, email address, phone number, physical location, your photo and employment and education history. There are certain required information fields which you must complete in order to create a Universal Profile and participate in the Talent Exchange.  The information you provide to us will be added to your Universal Profile on the Talent Exchange and will be accessible to other users of the Talent Exchange.      

We offer access to the Talent Exchange for potential employers on a for fee basis. Taleo has no control over the use of the data you share via the Talent Exchange by other Talent Exchange users and does not monitor any such use.  Taleo disclaims all liability to you for the use, disclosure, or dissemination by potential employers of information you have shared via the Talent Exchange.

Taleo may also disclose specific user information to third parties who are not users of the Talent Exchange when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to cooperate with or seek assistance from law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of Taleo or other users of the Talent Exchange. In addition, personal information we have collected may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy of Taleo.  

Your personally identifiable data, will be processed, stored and accessed in various global jurisdictions, including the United States.  Taleo may use third parties, including hosting co-location, hosting managed service providers and application providers, in various locations, including the United States, to operate the Talent Exchange and your personal data may be processed, stored and accessed by such third parties.  By accessing the Talent Exchange, you consent to such hosting and processing of your data.

You may delete your data from the Talent Exchange at any time by clicking on the “Delete Account” link that is located in the Settings section. and deleting the Taleo Radar application from your mobile device.
